<!DOCTYPE document PUBLIC "-//Apache Software Foundation//DTD XDOC 1.0//EN" "http://maven.apache.org/dtd/xdoc_1_0.dtd">
<!--

    Copyright (c) 2006-2009 Floggy Open Source Group. All rights reserved.

    Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
    you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
    You may obtain a copy of the License at

    http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

    Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
    distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
    WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
    See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
    limitations under the License.

-->
<document>
	<properties>
		<title>Welcome to Floggy</title>
		<author email="thiago.moreira@floggy.org">Thiago Moreira</author>
		<author email="thiago.rossato@floggy.org">Thiago Rossato</author>
	</properties>
	<body>
		<section name="News">
			<p><img src="images/starOn.png" alt="News" /><b> 16-Jan-10: The 1.3.1 maintenance release was made available, its target is fix an issue on Windows platform. Be aware of the <a href="./changes-report.html#a1.3.1">change</a>.</b></p>
			<p><img src="images/starOn.png" alt="News" /><b> 20-Dec-09: The 1.3.0 final release was made available, check the list of <a href="./changes-report.html#a1.3.0">changes</a>. Enjoy!</b></p>
			<p><b>18-Dec-09:</b> A new <a href="./qa.html">Q&amp;A</a> section was created. There you can check how we try to deliver a free of bug software.</p>
			<p><b>25-Aug-09:</b> A new snapshot release was made available. Six features was added. More <a href="./changes-report.html#a1.3.0-SNAPSHOT">here</a>.</p>
			<p><b>25-Aug-09:</b> Floggy now has a Fisheye tool linked to its source code. Check it out: <a href="http://fisheye3.atlassian.com/browse/floggy">http://fisheye3.atlassian.com/browse/floggy</a>.</p>
			<p>A complete list of news is available <a href="./news.html">here</a>. Stay tuned! Subscribe our <a href="https://sourceforge.net/export/rss2_keepsake.php?group_id=139426" >RSS</a> feed.<a href="https://sourceforge.net/export/rss2_keepsake.php?group_id=139426"><img src="images/rss.png" alt="RSS"/></a></p>
 		</section>
 		<section name="Welcome to Floggy">
 			<p>Floggy is a <b>free object persistence framework</b> for J2ME/MIDP applications. The main goal of this framework is to abstract the data persistence details from the developer, reducing the development and maintenance effort. How? Check the examples in the <a href="getting-started.html#framework">Getting Started</a> section.</p>
			<p>Floggy is licensed under the <a href="http://www.apache.org/licenses/" class="externalLink">Apache License, version 2.0</a>. That means that you can use Floggy in open source and commercial projects.</p>
			<p><i>Now you don't need to write thousands of lines of persistence code anymore. Floggy will do the dirty work for you!</i></p>
			<script type="text/javascript" src="http://w.sharethis.com/button/sharethis.js#tabs=web%2Cpost%2Cemail&amp;charset=utf-8&amp;style=rotate&amp;publisher=abd6676a-8a5c-48aa-9516-2aee60a788a9&amp;headerbg=%2323963c&amp;inactivefg=%23211d1d&amp;linkfg=%2323963c"></script>
 		</section>
 		<section name="Why Floggy?">
 			<p>As J2ME developers we couldn't handle anymore the idea of writing so many code lines to persist so few attributes. For each class we want to persist we had to developed the source code to transform an object into a byte array and vice-versa. We have tried to find free persistence frameworks for this technology on the internet, but we couldn't find one that fitted our needs. So, we have decided to start our own project.</p>
 		</section>
 		<section name="Architecture">
 			<p>Floggy is composed by 2 modules: </p>
			<ul>
				<li><a href="./persistence-framework/index.html">Framework</a>: Responsible for supplying persistence methods such as saving, removing and finding objects through a small API (11k) that must be attached to your application.</li>
				<li><a href="./persistence-weaver/index.html">Weaver</a>: Responsible for analyzing, generating and weaving bytecode into the persistable classes.</li>
			</ul>
			<p>The following process describes how Floggy works:</p>
			<img alt="" src="./images/persistence_process.jpg" /><p>Before you start using Floggy, we strongly recommend the reading of the <a href="./getting-started.html">getting started</a> section. </p>
		</section>
	</body>
</document>
